Hello everyone, do you remember me? I am your cute teacher Molly, and today I am your little C-Jun.
Next, are you curious about who will be our live streamer today?
Our live streamer today is Mr. Yan, who missed our live stream at the end of the year because he was half-naked.
Next, let's welcome Mr. Yan in a song. Everyone get ready.
Watching the sun shine, that is the color of the new year.
Listening to the bells ringing, that is the melody of the new year.
Dear fans of Bilibili, with this melodious melody, we welcome the first live stream of Claw in 2021.
I am your live streamer tonight, Mr. Yan.
Okay, we are going to start today's live stream.
Everyone get ready.
Get your small board and your paper.
Remember your notes.
Tonight we are going to talk about the first live stream of Claw in 2021.
The theme of the first live stream is to make the air more fresh.
I hope everyone will have a more prosperous year in 2021.
So our live stream is about to start.
Okay, let's take a look at the content of today's live stream.
First of all, we are going to import the clothes that we have previously announced to you.
This material has already been given to everyone.
Did you download it in advance?
Okay, we have given you the version of this dress before.
Then let's take a look at this dress.
It's a set with a down jacket and a pair of pants.
Okay, first of all, let's talk about how we make such a washing machine for your clothes.
Let's find our hat version.
You will find that this side has the position of the cow's feet drawn in advance.
First of all, we need to convert this base line into an internal line.
Everyone should know how to do it.
Okay, let's wait patiently.
After we convert it to the base line,
let's take a look at the position of the two internal lines.
The position of the internal line.
Next, we need to convert it to a new version.
In order to make it run faster,
we will freeze the other unused versions first.
Okay, let's convert the version.
First of all, let's measure the length of one side of this cow's foot.
You can see that this side is 76.4.
Okay, everyone, pay attention.
This is 76.4.
We click the left button and press the right button to enter the dialogue box.
76.4, convert to a straight line.
Then we press the Ctrl key to start converting to a curve.
Convert to our board.
You have to pay attention, young people.
You have to convert to a board.
Okay, let's adjust the shape of the board.
What is the conversion?
It's a bit like a cow's foot.
You can think of it as a sandpaper, right?
And then what about the next?
Our feet are a little big.
Okay, next.
Let's make it a little smaller.
Make the line a little shorter.
We can see that there is some damage to the board.
It's because our particle diameter is relatively large at the moment.
Let's make it a little smaller.
Reduce the particle diameter.
Yes.
Okay, the next step is to sew half of the cow's foot to one side of our circle.
Sew to one side.
Then we add this cow's foot board to the outside of the hat.
Then let's take a look.
Move to the sewing box position.
Okay, let's click on the simulation.
Okay, after the simulation, let's come to its front.
Look at the shape of this cow's foot.
You can see that this cow's foot is a little big.
We have to manually make it a little smaller.
Make it a little smaller.
In this way, I'm in its sharp position.
Add a straight line to it.
Then use the editor tool to manually make this cow's foot a little smaller.
If you like a bigger cow's foot, you can draw a bigger cow's foot.
Okay, you can see that this shape is a little more suitable.
Next, we need to copy the other side of the cow's foot.
Let's make it a colon layer.
Very simple.
You can also copy it out with Ctrl C and Ctrl V.
Okay, we can untie it.
Next, we need to sew the other side of the cow's foot.
We can see that there is a sewing line here.
Delete it.
Then use the sewing line to sew it up.
Okay.
Then sew the cow's foot together with the cap.
Okay, the sewing is done.
Let's take a look at its effect.
It looks pretty good.
Let's take a look at its front.
You will find that after we sew the cow's foot,
the cow's foot does not feel very full.
It's a little flat.
At this time, you can choose our board.
Harden it.
After hardening it,
the shape of the cow's foot will be a little rounder.
A little rounder.
Let's turn it around and check its shape.
After the cow's foot is done on one side,
we can directly use Ctrl D
to align it and copy the board to the other side.
Copy it out.
Okay.
Let's move the position of our cow's foot.
Let's move its position.
Okay.
You can see that the two of our cow's feet have been done.
Doesn't it look a little more lively?
In addition to hardening,
we can also add a sticky layer to our board.
For this sticky layer,
we can set its properties.
Choose a harder sticky layer.
In this way,
even if we are in a state of non-hardening,
it will still look fuller.
We don't need to keep hardening it.
You can see that the cow's foot still looks more handsome.
Okay.
Let's adjust its size again.
It's a little big.
Why didn't my cow's foot collapse?
Because I didn't collapse.
Why didn't I collapse?
Because I hardened it.
Didn't you see it?
Listen to the lesson carefully.
Don't be so fierce.
Okay.
Next,
let's draw a cow's ear board like this.
As you know,
this cow's ear is still very cute.
Okay.
First of all,
let's measure the length of the inner line.
Let's draw one of the lines of the cow's ear.
47.5
Then let's draw a shape like a peach.
Let's draw a shape.
We draw a shape right now.
What do we draw?
First we draw the shape of the cow's ear.
It is a peach.
It's a peach.
Let's draw a shape.
Let's draw a symbol.
Then how to adjust it? Let's select our board
Select the board, I want to extend the position of the two sides of the board
Extend a part out
Let's take a look
Everyone needs to look carefully at this place, I want to extend a part out
How long does it extend? Extend 25mm
The other side is the same
I'll sell a coffin here first
Guess what it's for
Then I'll take the position that just extended in the middle
Add this straight line point
Okay, after adding the straight line point
We're going to use this edit board
Use this
Uh, the sewing tool to sew up the two sides of this point
Let him sew it up
You can guess what I'm going to do in the chat
Guess what
Okay, let's take a look at this
Sew up the two sides like this
Don't forget to change the type of sewing line after sewing
And then?
Let's take the middle
Your original part with our cow
This position on the hat is sewn together
Then I used a shortcut key
Ctrl plus big capital
Add it to the outside of our board
And I saw someone say it was a roll head
We'll take a look, will we
Okay, let's print this board
Hey our board is lined up
You can see it
The fan just answered correctly
It's a roll head
But what about this ear?
It's a little bit out of sync
We're going to use this one at this point
You can use our grid tool
Use the grid tool to find it in the 3D window
And then?
Use our grid tool to drag the other side of the ear to drag it out
Yeah, drag it out
Let's do it again
Do it again
Hey, hey
You can see this ear coming out
Right?
This ear came out
But this ear looks a little bit long
Let's shorten it a little bit
Okay, let's wait for him to simulate
Let's move the position of the inner line
Adjust the ear forward
I feel like he's a little bit behind
Next?
After we've done the side of the ear
It's still like a bullfrog
The other side
The other side of the ear is also copied out
You copy it out
Move the position
What's next?
We're going to take the bull's ear
It's also two layers for him
Make him a colon layer
What about the two sides?
It's all the same for him to make this colon layer
And then?
We can take a look at it
What's the effect of two layers of bull ears
Now?
He's still hardening
And then?
I'm going to take this plate and choose it
Get rid of hardening
Let's simulate it
Okay, you can see if it's this little ear
Is there any of this in the middle
Is it a little bit of a wrinkle
Is it very serious
It looks very cute
You want to pinch it
Do it yourself
Don't pinch my ears
Someone else said the bull's ear is not pretty
The bull's ear is not pretty, it's not good to eat it
Isn't that right
All right, let's take a look at this ear
We're going to make it
His ears and his feet
We've done it for him
And then?
Let's put this ear and feet on a separate piece of fabric for him
Let's make him a golden corner and a golden ear
It's a very new year atmosphere
Let's take a look at his color
Let's change our type first
Remember that we can apply this fabric to this metal type
And then?
Let's give him a color change
Yellow is gold
Then you can see this after the color is adjusted
This one
This one is too golden
Let's give him a little adjustment
Some of the parameters below
Let's adjust it first
Adjust the roughness of the surface
Make it a little bigger
In this case, it's a little bit like this
The texture of the sand
It's not as good as it was just now
Then we have this bull's foot and the bull's ear
It's done
You practice it yourself in the back
And then?
What about the other positions?
For him to do it
We're going to turn it upside down
Turn the board upside down
After the return, we're going to take the board
Give him a general simulation
Put our bull's ear bull's foot and our clothes together
Simulate together
So after we're done with the simulation
We can reduce the particle diameter of the board
Give him a decrease
I was going to make it higher
Easy to simulate
I'm going to make it all five
Let's lower it a little bit
All right, let's give him a simulation
Okay, I'm going to add another layer
So he's now suspicious
Assign a new layer
And we're going to do the same thing
Okay, I'm going to go ahead and give him two layers
Make it a little bit smaller
And then we're going to lower the particle diameter
Let him a big feeling
And then we're going to give him more
Let it go
When you're done
Or can you give him three layers
Let's see
It's pretty good
Okay, let's give him a simulation
Okay, that's it
I'm going to simulate it
Okay, in that case, we go through a simple simulation
What about our clothes?
Next, let's talk about the print editor.
First, let's add a sticker to it.
We choose a new year image of a warrior.
Let's talk about the function of the print editor.
The teacher just changed a new computer.
The computer runs very fast.
It's not lagging at all.
Let's make the size of the sticker a little bigger.
Next, let's choose a fabric for the jacket.
Let's choose a fabric for the jacket to do the print design.
First, let's choose it.
You can see that behind the text,
you will find that
we have added the function of opening the print editor.
After we open it,
it will pop into a dialogue box.
First, we need to add a texture.
Then, let's enter the print editor.
Let's add a texture first.
Then, let's choose our texture editor.
In the texture editor,
we can see that there will be a dialogue box here.
We can choose our different textures.
It's like a layer here.
There can be textures.
The top is the size of our picture.
You can adjust it on it.
There are some other parameters here.
For example, you can adjust the grid,
the circle transparency, and so on.
You can adjust it here.
Next, let's choose the texture.
In the texture,
we can see that there are colors,
mixing,
transparency,
flatness,
extension to the other side,
and so on.
There are different options.
You can also see that there is a small lock and a trash can
on the right side of the texture.
In this case,
you will find that
it is very similar to the layer function in our PS.
If you choose it,
you can do some mixing for this layer.
There is a mixing mode,
and so on.
You can change the color.
First, let's choose this color.
You can take a look at it.
We can change it here.
We can also use our color meter
to use the texture
to match the color on the sticker.
Let's adjust the color.
After we have adjusted the color,
click OK.
Let's take a look at this red.
Next,
you can adjust the transparency of our color,
and some other parameters.
Next,
we click Add.
What does this add?
It adds something like this.
You can see that
this is a small PNG sticker.
This small sticker is
what we share with you as material.
It is also drawn by our teacher.
Yes,
you must use it.
We choose this small sticker.
You must remember that
we must use transparent PNG here.
Then,
we choose one of the stickers.
We choose a flower like this.
Click Open.
Then,
we can see that
the sticker here
will be added to our material.
In our material,
we will find that
this sticker is very small.
We can choose this sticker
to adjust its size
and position
through the function of
the right-hand corner of the screen reader.
You can adjust it here.
We can see that
there is also a flat slope below.
It is to fill it up.
We can adjust the flat slope,
then shrink,
shrink,
and then check your design.
The smaller one is denser,
and the larger one is larger.
Okay,
let's adjust it manually.
At the same time,
we will find that
the position of the sticker in the gap
does not appear,
only half.
We can extend it to the other side.
In this way,
it will not affect our design.
At the same time,
here we can also choose
the different mixing modes of our stickers.
For example,
normal,
flat slope,
and flat slope.
This is very similar to our PS function.
You can try it yourself.
It is very interesting.
We can make a lot of different
print designs
through a simple one or two elements.
Now we adjust it back to the stack.
We can see
the effect of the stack.
Next,
we can add color to the sticker.
Add color.
I will change it back to normal now.
Let's take a look at
the effect of the stack of different colors.
We can take the color of the lion
and make a combination.
You can do it according to your own design.
You can do it as you like.
Now we can adjust it as you like.
There are different colors between different colors.
What kind of color do we use?
For example,
red,
green,
or green.
Let's see.
Red will be the color of our stars.
See,
they are gold.
The red color of the stars will change to a different color.
This will make the colors turn more or less purple.
The color of the stars will change for different colors.
Now we have two colors in different colors.
We can use the color from our palette
to change the color of the stars
That's it
We're going to fill in this sticker
Fill it in and put it in
Slowly adjust it
Next, we can go to this sticker
Do multiple increases and duplicates
You can click on it to duplicate it
You can see that it becomes a different effect
Right?
A big flower comes out
Then we can also select this single layer
You can duplicate it multiple times to make a combination
We can see this
This is what I did just now
A simple combination of the effect
Let's add a new different element
To make some combinations
The elements I chose today
Are all related to Chinese traditional materials
For example, jade and flowers
Some traditional materials
I hope you like it
I hope you like this
Then we can go together
Then we can see its effect through the flat pattern design method
If I want to do some other design effects
Such as gold
Or other methods
We'll talk about other effects later
Then we can also see
This sticker and add color
Let's see its effect
After the design is done, we can click on the application, remember to click on the application, if you do not click on the application, it will not be read, click on the application.
Then let's remove the texture editor, we can select the fabric, click on the pattern here, you can see that it will automatically generate a four-sided continuous sticker here, which is convenient for us to export it.
Next, we can see that there is a function called add print on the back of our fabric, we click on it and it will enter our pattern.
The way to use it is the same as our texture editor.
First of all, we click on the pattern.
First select a pattern and click on open.
After opening, the print cloth will add a new layer of print on your original fabric.
Let's take a look at one of its effects.
My northeast yellow ear is noisy, right?
Ok, the new print cloth we added is our little cloud.
We can change the type of print cloth here, change it to a metal material like this.
In this way, we can give our clothing the effect of making gold.
You can select the pattern behind the pattern and adjust the size to it.
We can select the pattern and rotate it, rotate it, zoom in and zoom out, and change the color, etc.
We can adjust a yellow color like this.
Make it a little golden gold.
At the same time, we can use the texture editor to duplicate the pattern to create a layer of gold.
As you can see, it looks a little hazy.
That's right, I am such an overbearing person.
I am such an overbearing person.
Some people say that I am overbearing, so I can sell it to the Hainan branch.
You can think about what the big flower-shaped earring Zhu Jielun wears.
I will invite Zhu Jielun to wear it on our company's Hechuan Road one day.
Let's adjust the color of the other little cloud.
We can adjust the color of the other little cloud.
We can see that such a cloth is quickly transformed from a white bottom to a very new year-like big flower-shaped earring.
You can make thisistui, you can make thisistui, you can make thisistui, you can make thisistui.
In theштiesbu, if I can use myระindu조
First, let's turn off the
stabilizer and go to the stabilizer side.
Let's take a look at this side.
There is such a small sticker here.
You can do your other design with a small sticker.
Let's take a look at the northeast flower we made.
Next, let's take a look at the color window.
Can we also do such a multi-layer effect design?
Next, let's enter the color window.
We also click on the texture by creating a new style.
In the texture side,
we also select some pasted materials to create.
Let's enter the color of the texture.
First, let's make a color selection for the bottom of the fabric.
Let's choose such a nice blue.
Nice green.
It's all right.
You say blue, it's blue.
You say green, it's green.
Blue and green again.
Do you think this is blue or green?
Let's adjust it like this.
In the same way,
we also add such a small sticker
on the cotton cloth.
Then we can adjust its size through the multi-layer effect.
Let's do your creative design.
This is still pretty good.
This color combination.
Then,
we're going to go to this color combination.
Let's change the color of the cloud.
Then we can take the color of our lion's head.
Let's match it.
Let's adjust it.
This is still quite auspicious.
If everyone wears this to go home for the New Year,
there will definitely be no elders to say anything.
Okay.
Next,
we also add a cherry blossom cloth to this new color.
Let's do some combination matching.
Don't care if it looks good or not.
We mainly teach you the use of this new tool.
Don't care about these details.
You said it looks good.
I think it looks good.
This is my design.
Can I say it doesn't look good?
Are you kidding me?
You're right.
Okay.
Then,
let's see the new sticker.
We can use the same method just now.
It's also to change the material type of it.
Change it to metal.
Then,
go to the multi-layer effect.
Choose this cherry blossom.
To adjust its size.
To place it,
and so on.
Everyone must remember.
Remember the combination of the two tools we just told you.
Don't care if I do it well or not.
The way is the key.
Let's place it like this.
Let's adjust its color.
Put a round of red sun.
Then,
we can add a layer of the same color.
Just like this.
Okay.
Then,
click it.
we can change the color of the detail.
Just like this.
Then,
we can change the color of the detail.
Just like that.
Then,
we can adjust the color of the detail.
Just like this.
It's the same.
We can adjust the color of the detail.
Let's go to the application.
OK.
We can also click on the application.
Let's continue to add more stickers.
Since the sun is there,
there must be clouds,
right?
This way,
we can symbolize
the sky.
The icon
refers to the multi-cloud transition in the weather forecast.
Similarly, we can also adjust the top and bottom layers between the two stickers on the layer here.
You can put the clouds in the back, so that it belongs to the multi-cloud transition.
We click on the application.
We click on update and we will find that we have two of these colors in this dress.
Because I just adjusted the cherry blossom fabric, so the design of the cherry blossom fabric in the front has been changed.
Let's change it again and hang the cherry blossom fabric out again to change the effect of the red cherry blossom fabric.
There is a student who said that the model is not happy with her face full.
Is it like when you go home in the New Year and your mother puts on a cotton cloth?
It's like when you get married.
Yes, it's like when you get dressed in an autumn dress.
Let's rotate it to see the effect.
Finally, let's go back to the model window.
Next, let's blur this dress.
Let's see what the effect of blurring looks like.
Let's take a look at the blurring here.
The effect of blurring is still very good.
Because of this red color, you will find that it is a little dark in the window.
But the blurring will be better.
It's a little softer, isn't it?
Do you remember that classic line?
Pink is a little tender.
How old are you now?
Okay, let's stop the blurring.
You will find that the color of our inner layer is too white.
Let's add some cherry blossoms to it.
Let's take a look at the design of the inner layer.
Our little C-jun is already...
Laughed to death.
Okay, let's select our version to see which fabric it is.
Then select this new fabric.
Let's add a texture to it.
Enter our texture editor.
Next, let's add a cherry blossom to it.
The color of this cherry blossom is white.
Let's adjust the color.
For example, this.
Okay, let's take a look.
After the adjustment, the cloth inside...
Will have a light cherry blossom.
Or still very good looking.
Laugh.
Let's be serious.
It's a little shiny.
Let's add a little color here.
Change the color source of our shirt.
Let's add a little pink.
Add some other colors.
Let's adjust the color of this shirt.
Then let's adjust the color of this shirt.
Add some green.
Let's add some red.
As you can see, the size of the cloud is the largest of the three windows.
If you want to adjust its size, you can adjust its width on the top.
You can make your cherry blossoms a little bigger.
Here I adjust its size.
Let's zoom in on the cherry blossoms.
You will find that our clothes have a hollow effect.
That's because we haven't adjusted the bottom yet.
Let's adjust the bottom later.
Let's choose the bottom layer of white texture.
Select it, and adjust its size to the same as the top layer.
This way, we can fill the whole picture.
This way, we can manually adjust the size of the cherry blossoms.
You can adjust its size according to your design.
Then, we can adjust the height of the cherry blossoms.
This way, we can adjust their height.
The orange color is so bright.
OK, let's zoom in and see its effect.
Next, let's open the next layer.
I'm going to adjust the size by suggesting this aspect.
This is for the orange color.
Who is saying that I am a half wolf?
Ok, let's come to our cow version
This cow is designed by the teacher today
Isn't it very cute?
Cute, cute, applause, applause
From the recognition of the cow
Next, let's make this white cow
A red cow like this
First, let's add a texture to the texture
Then open our texture editor
First, let's turn this cow into a red cow
There is no advertising for red cows here
Don't think too much
Then let's add a cherry
This little flower cow's cherry is still very cute
Ok, let's adjust the size of this flower
Let's add a few more sets of small materials
Let's combine them to see the effect
Ok, someone asked how to make this cow
Please look forward to our next live broadcast
We will teach you how to make a cow
Let's continue to do some design
Make more cherry blossoms
There are too many cherry blossoms
Let's reduce the transparency of the cherry blossoms
Let's take a look
This cow is ourül
Ok, let's adjust the place of the cherry blossom
A bit heavy color
Let's adjust this color by some colors
You can view this how to make the cherry blossoms
traits in laterывает
Then we will make the color of the cherry blossom a little lighter
Yes, this cow is so cute, right?
Do you want one?
Ok, we click on the application
Next, we will add a cherry blossom cloth to our cherry blossoms
Click on the cloud
Then we enter the cloud into the document editor
Make some adjustments to its size and position
We change its type to yellow
Then we add some metal to it
We also add some gold to it
It means that our new year is going to be wonderful
What kind of word is this?
I'm sorry
This is a cheap literary foundation
Next, let's show off this cute cow
Some fans asked what is the fabric of our cow's feet
The fabric of our cow's feet is the fabric of the needlework
The fabric of the needlework
Ok, let's refresh it
Look at the effect of the cow after the rendering
It's coming out
Isn't it very cute?
This cow is very thick
We can see that this cow is a little bit shiny now
If we want to make this cow into a cute and fluffy cow
How can we do?
We can choose the fabric
Ok, today we will have a class of extra meals
Teach you how to make a cow
Ok, let's click on our material type
Change it to fur
Change it to hair
Let's click on the rendering to check its effect
Ok, after a brief rendering
Ok, here it is
Heaven and heaven
Please be careful
This is a local cow
You deserve to
The length of the fur is too long
We will shorten it
This is a special cow tutorial today
Cow live
Next, we will customize it
Why is the cow mid-distance
This cow is mid-distance
It represents the cow more
More deep
Haha
Don't say my cow is like a pig
Ha ha
Let's see if we can adjust the length of the hair
Reduce the length of the hair
Now we have changed it to 30
Let's continue to render
Let's see if the teacher's computer is rendering very fast
The hair rendering is also very fast
How do you ask his eyes
Eyes in the middle
Didn't you see it
Such two big eyes
You didn't see it
Did you see it
The eyes of Jiong Jiong
It looks like he's not looking at you smartly
You can see this cow
That's what he's doing right now
The thickness of the hair is including the thickness
And some density
We can make some adjustments
We can make some slight adjustments
Let's first make his density a little higher
Let's adjust it to 800 first
And this is what we're going to do
So that the hair should look a little longer
And then it should look a little bit more natural
And then it's going to look a little bit more natural
So if I want to change this hair
Let's make it bigger
I'm going to change the layer of hair
To 100
To that
Let's adjust it to 800
and you can see that the hair will look a little bit more voluminous
When we record
It will look a little bit more fashionable
We can adjust its length a little bit
Let's change the density to 1000 to see the effect
This is the result
It's very cute
We have shared this version with you on WeChat
You can leave comments on WeChat
Don't leave weird comments
You can get the material of this cow
This cow is very soft
I want to hug it
Let's rotate to see the next shot
See the effect of the cow from different angles
After the cow is done
I will show you how to use the new function
Laser
Today is the color change
To make some fashionable stickers
And how to make some straight lines
This is the effect
Let's wait for it to render
Now
Let's go to this dress
Next, let's talk about the laser sticker
The color change sticker
And how to make straight lines
First, delete the sticker
And add a new sticker
Wait a moment
We need to refresh it
Let's open the material of the cloud
Where to put the material
In our cloud
We can see that
The color change is the same
As the color change
Where to put the material
In our WeChat public number
You can see in the lower left corner
The QR code of WeChat public number
You can scan the code
Follow our public number
Leave a message in the back
And get the material
Let's choose this sticker
Let's adjust the size of the sticker
Let's change its type here
Change the type here to the color change
This is the light above
Change to the color change
Click it
Under normal 3D mode, we can't see the effect of the color change, so we need to enter the rendering mode.
Click Render, click refresh to see the effect of the color change.
You can see that there is a color change effect in the middle.
We can see its color change effect from different angles.
Next, we can adjust the color of the image.
To make the color change effect stronger.
There are many parameters that can be adjusted.
You can try it yourself.
Next, I will show you how to make the color change effect.
Let's take a look at the promotional picture.
There is a cloud on the sleeve.
The cloud has a soft texture.
It looks like the color change effect that we usually design.
Let's see how to make the color change effect.
First of all.
We still need to import a sticker.
This sticker is also used for fixed materials.
Click on this cloud.
Click on open.
Then we open this cloud.
Let's enter rendering to see the effect of the rendering.
This is an ordinary sticker.
Next, let's choose this sticker.
Let's change the property of the sticker to hair.
We can see that the hair is very long.
Let's make it a little shorter.
Does it remind you of the buffalo just now?
It's a little short.
Let's make it a little longer.
Let's make the density a little bigger.
Okay, we can see this.
After we make the density bigger.
The position of our cloud.
You will find that its hair is not only on the cloud.
It also has its surroundings.
What's the reason?
If you want to use hairs in your sticker.
We're going to add a default picture here.
We pull down.
There's a default picture below.
Click on the default picture.
There are length, thickness and density below.
We click on the density.
Then we will use a default image created by XiangYun to import it
How to make this default image?
Just add a black background to it with your own sticker
And color your picture
It's a gray picture
The black position represents that it doesn't grow hair
The white position represents that it grows hair
It will have such a fingerprint effect
Let's take a look
Let's import it
Open it
Let's show it
As you can see, the rest of it doesn't have hair
Only the cloud has hair
Next, we will make the cloud a little smaller
Let's make the cloud a little bigger
A little bolder
We can directly do the design in the 3D window
Forces let's copy this
skinny
I will copy it
After
Aha
Let's copy the position of the sticker to it
Now let's go back to the rendering window to check the rendering effect.
Let's change the length of the hair.
When you are editing hair, you have to do it slowly.
Try to adjust the properties one by one.
If you are interested in hair, you can watch the previous video about hair rendering.
Let's check the side effect.
Let's make it a little longer.
When we are rendering white hair, the color is always black, right?
It doesn't look bright or white.
Why is that?
Because we need to adjust the rendering settings.
Where?
We can find the rendering settings on the top.
We need to adjust the light source and properties.
The light source and properties.
From here.
We can adjust the medium and the highest.
Adjust to very high.
That's it.
Let's render again.
Let's see.
The hair is rendered.
After adjustment, let's see.
You can see the hair is very bright.
It's white.
It's light.
There.
It's not.
OK, how about it.
And when you say it and
If you are recording it.
You can mess around like that.
that's it.
Next, let's look at some questions from our students
First, let's look at the question about the version of the cow
Let's take a look at the version of the cow
Click on our import dxf to find our desktop
Click on the cow and click open
Because our desktop is relatively small
Some of our fans found that they couldn't import our desktop
Remember to click on the import dxf to find our desktop
The cow's desktop is imported
It's very simple, isn't it?
Because the cow's desktop is a bit small
In some places, look at this small corner
Basically, the grid can't stand up
So there will be some problems when importing
Let's see if there are any other questions
There is a friend who wants you to make the cow's feet again
He said that the network was stuck
This one
Make the cow's feet again
Okay
Today, the teacher will meet your New Year's wishes
After you finish your homework, it will be a must to buy a new T-shirt
If you want a new T-shirt for your new T-shirt
Come to the T-shirt store
In order to buy a T-shirt, you need to get off work
You need to buy a T-shirt
If you buy a T-shirt, it will be for the New Year's gift
Also, you can also buy a T-shirt from other stores
You can buy a figure
You can get a T-shirt, your T-shirt, or a star
You also have a T-shirt
T-shirt
Now
the T-shirt
If you want to use T-shirts
You can buy a T-shirt
at the T-shirt store
You can also buy a T-shirt
Ok, let's freeze it all
Let's take a look at another method of teaching
First of all, let's use this tool to determine the length of the two corners of the curve
Let's draw a curve
0.5
OK
Then we can use the Ctrl key to draw a shape of the two corners of the curve
Let me adjust it
OK
Let's reduce the particle diameter of the two corners of the curve
Let's draw a curve
Here we are
And if we add another curve here
We can use the Temple command line to add a new curve
So what we can see is that
We can draw a curve for one position
Add the cowhide to the outside of the hat
And then we'll simulate it
You can see that the cowhide has been modified
If you want to adjust the size, you can add a dot in the middle
To adjust the cowhide size
And now we can replicate it
Or you can add a layer to cover it
If you want it to be easier, you can add an inner layer
Then we'll put the cowhide outside and outside together
And then put the inside of the cow's feet on top of the inside of the cow's feet
Then our cow's feet will be sewn up, right?
After sewing up, if you feel that your cow's feet are not full
You can choose the cow's feet and then press the right key to print it
Isn't this cow's foot fuller, right?
If we don't want to print it, we can also choose our cow's feet version
In the following, find the sticky layer and add a sticky layer
For this sticky layer, we have to choose a harder sticky layer
Click on the simulation
Finally, we can remove the hardening
This layer is a little soft, let's change to a harder layer
In this way, we can make such a cute cow's foot
Every time I draw a cow's foot, the version is different
Are there any other questions?
Let's take a look
I didn't see the teacher's real person
See you next time
This one
There are students who say that this pressure inflow is also possible
Yes, the pressure inflow is also possible
But after my experiment, I found that the pressure is actually very large
It doesn't have the effect of adding a sticky layer directly
And this is the cow's foot
The hat on the cow's foot must be oval
If you draw a line like a cow's ear
It's not easy to make it three-dimensional
This should be noted
How does the double layer of the cow's ear make the effect of bulging?
If you add a inner layer, it's okay
It's the effect of bulging
Right?
Yes
What do you think of the hardness of the sticky layer?
You can take a look at the preview of our sticky layer
The hardness is from the first one down
It's a little bit harder if it's the main layer down
There's a backrest here
It's suitable for, for example, pockets, collar, etc.
We click on the sticky layer
You can see its details
Find its details
The ones below are usually harder
Do you have any new questions?
Our live broadcast is coming to an end
The cotton cloth that falls in one direction
What kind of cotton cloth is that?
Do you think this is a shawl?
After we apply the hair
What about our hair?
Take a look
The hair here
It has this bending strength
You can adjust its bending strength
You can decide whether it is straight or bent
If you have to use your hand to wave this hair
There's no way
Great
There are people who praise me
Do you have any new questions?
If you don't have any questions
We're coming to an end
We can go and pick one for you
Elegant music
For the skin
You can use
It should be done with silk
The skin can be done with silk
You use silk to adjust it
Adjust the silk
Take a look
The intensity of the front color
Right
Adjust the intensity of the front color
Use silk
Then adjust the intensity of the front color
The method is up to you
Everyone has time to practice
Do you have any more questions?
Our live broadcast is next week
No questions
Stay tuned
So how does it look
To the my
What to do with the dress
Here is what you did
last's dress
We're wearing the navy clothes
You can go and watch the performance from last episode
Yes
The first song is for you to sing.
singing